<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>self management on log from home</title>
    <link>https://blog.lofibean.cc/tags/self-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in self management on log from home</description>
    <image>
      
      <url>https://blog.lofibean.cc/android-chrome-512x512.png?v=20201231</url>
      
      <title>Favicon of self management on log from home</title>
      <link>https://blog.lofibean.cc/</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; bemnlam</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 13:33:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.lofibean.cc/tags/self-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should Manage Your Energy, Not Your Time</title>
      <link>https://blog.lofibean.cc/posts/why-you-should-manage-your-energy-not-your-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 13:33:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.lofibean.cc/posts/why-you-should-manage-your-energy-not-your-time/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-summary&#34;&gt;🎯 Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a human being, &lt;strong&gt;managing our energy is more important&lt;/strong&gt; because this is a limited resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may wrongly think that increasing working hours can do more. However, longer working hours leads more &lt;strong&gt;unfocus&lt;/strong&gt; time and brings negative effect to your work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, having a monthly plan is better then a detailed daily plan. The later one demotivated people because we face &lt;strong&gt;inevitable distractions&lt;/strong&gt; daily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-thoughts&#34;&gt;💡 Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay focus on work by taking regular breaks. (e.g &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pomodoro_Technique&#34;&gt;Pomodoro Technique&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the article, top 10% productive employees &lt;strong&gt;work 52-mins work and take 17-mins break&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly schedule some time for work individually without distraction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;--highlights&#34;&gt;⭐️  Highlights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A workplace study found an average working professional experiences 87 interruptions per day, making it difficult to remain productive and focused for a full day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the top 10 percent of employees with the highest productivity didn’t put in longer hours than anyone else – often they didn&amp;rsquo;t even work eight-hour days. Instead, the key to their productivity was that for every 52 minutes of focused work, they took a 17-minute break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At any given point, I should have deep work scheduled for roughly the next month. Once on the calendar, I protect this time like I would a doctor’s appointment or important meeting,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the researchers assumed that the well-structured daily plans would be most effective when it came to the execution of tasks, they were wrong: the detailed daily plans demotivated students. Harford argues that inevitable distractions often render the daily to-do list ineffective, while leaving room for improvisation in such a list can reap the best results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;-reference&#34;&gt;🔗 reference:&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://getpocket.com/explore/item/why-you-should-manage-your-energy-not-your-time&#34;&gt;Why You Should Manage Your Energy, Not Your Time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
